[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
- Coming up next, another episode of America's
接下来，《美国最受欢迎的真人秀》
favorite reality show, "The Life of Eiffel."
《埃菲尔的生活》
- With me, Eiffel!
和我一起，埃菲尔！
- Ugh, when I was in ballet class with Eiffel,
唉，我和埃菲尔一起上芭蕾课时，
I couldn't stand her.
我受不了她。
But now that she's on TV, I love her.
但现在她在电视上，我就喜欢她了。
- Me too.
我也是。
- Me three.
- Me three, too.
我也是。
♪ ♪
- I'm your sister.
- 我是你姐姐。
You can't have family game night without me.
没有我，你们不能举行家庭游戏之夜。
- Sorry, Eiffel, you make it odd.
- 对不起，埃菲尔，你让气氛变得奇怪。
- So? We can play two against three.
- 那又怎样？我们可以二对三玩。
- No. I meant, like, you make it odd
- 不，我的意思是，你让气氛变得奇怪，
because, ya know, you're odd.
因为，你知道，你本身就很奇怪。
- Ugh!
- 呃！
Odd?
奇怪？
I'm not odd!
我才不奇怪！
I'm odd-dacious!
我是古怪至极！
I can't believe you don't want me at your game night.
我真不敢相信你不想让我参加你的游戏之夜。
I'm America's toilet paper princess!
我是美国的厕纸公主！
When people wipe their tushies, all they think about
当人们擦屁股时，他们满脑子想的都是
is this face.
这张脸。
- I know I do.
我知道我会的。
- Fine!
好吧！
I'll have my own game night.
我会举办我自己的游戏之夜。
With better games and better snacks.
有更好的游戏和更好的零食。
But you know what it won't have?
但你知道它不会有的是什么吗？
You, Lilly.
你，莉莉。
You.
你。
Eiffel out!
出去！
[all screaming]
[所有人尖叫]
- Okay, who's hurt? all: Shh!
- 好吧，谁受伤了？所有人：嘘！
- Anyone bleeding? all: Shh!
- 有人流血吗？所有人：嘘！
- I think one of 'em sprung a leak.
- 我觉得其中一个漏气了。
- No one's hurt.
- 没人受伤。
- We were just watching "The Life of Eiffel."
- 我们只是在看《埃菲尔的一生》。
- With her, Eiffel.
- 和她一起，埃菲尔。
- This episode is so good.
- 这一集太精彩了。
- Lilly's having game night and uninvited Eiffel.
- 莉莉举办游戏之夜，却没邀请艾菲尔。
- Because she thinks she's odd.
- 因为她觉得艾菲尔很古怪。
- So then Eiffel was all, "Ugh, I'm not odd...
- 于是艾菲尔就说，“哼，我才不古怪呢……
I'm odd-dacious."
- 我是古怪得不得了。”
But then Lilly was all, "Ghost out, toilet paper princess.
- 但莉莉却说，“快消失吧，卫生纸公主。
Around here, you're number two."
- 在这里，你只能排第二。”
[all giggling]
- [大家都笑了起来]
- Have you guys been watching this all day?
- 你们一整天都在看这个吗？
- Well, the day's not over yet,
- 嗯，今天还没结束呢，
but that was our goal, yes.
但那是我们的目标，是的。
- Yeah, it's not like we're addicted to it or anything.
是的，我们并没有沉迷于此。
- Oh, well then you won't mind if I turn it off.
哦，那你不介意我把它关掉吧。
- No, no, no, no! - Dad!
不，不，不，不！- 爸爸！
- Why did the bad man take my friends away?
为什么坏人把我的朋友们带走了？
- I'm sorry, kids, but it's time you "ghosted" out of this show.
对不起，孩子们，但现在是你们‘消失’的时候了。
- "Ghosted," Dad?
‘消失’，爸爸？
Don't try to sound young.
别试图装年轻。
- You kids need to stop watching other people's TV lives,
你们这些孩子需要停止观看别人的电视生活，
and start living your own lives.
开始过自己的生活。
- You don't understand.
- 你不明白。
They're rich and famous.
他们很有钱也很出名。
Their TV lives are way more interesting than our real lives.
他们的电视生活比我们的真实生活有趣多了。
- True dat.
- 确实如此。
- Dat not true.
- 那不是真的。
- Now it's just sad.
- 现在这变得有点悲哀了。
- Listen, I'm just saying, you're interesting.
- 听着，我只是想说，你们也很有趣。
- Yeah, you're quadruplets.
- 是的，你们是四胞胎。
Do you know how many sets of quads there are in the world?
你知道世界上有多少四胞胎吗？
- 3,556.
- 3,556。
You asked!
你问的！
- All I'm saying is that if you just got off the couch
我只是说，如果你从沙发上起来
and did something, maybe you could be rich and famous.
做点什么，也许你就能变得富有和出名。
- What do we do now?
我们现在做什么？
- What's the purpose of our lives if we can't
如果我们不能
watch other people's lives on TV?
在电视上看别人的生活，那我们生活的意义是什么？
- Wait...
等等...
that's it!
就是这样！
Mom and Dad are right.
爸爸妈妈是对的。
We're every bit as interesting as Eiffel and Lilly.
我们和艾菲尔和莉莉一样有趣。
We should just make a reality show about ourselves.
我们应该做一个关于自己的真人秀。
- Yeah!
没错！
I mean, we may not be odd-dacious,
我是说，我们可能不算怪诞，
but we're quad-dacious.
但我们是四胞胎啊。
- We'll be a bigger hit than "The Life of Eiffel."
- 我们会比《艾菲尔的生活》更火。
- And then once we're rich and famous,
- 等我们有了名又有了钱，
we can watch anything we want, anytime we want.
就能随时随地看我们想看的了。
- Well, when we're not jet-skiing
嗯，只要我们不在巨型布丁池里骑水上摩托。
in a giant pool of pudding.
我们要发财了。
We're gonna be rich.
大胆想象，伙计们。
Think big, guys.
要有大志，伙计们。
[upbeat music]
[欢快音乐]
♪ ♪
- [whistling]
- [吹口哨]
♪ ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪ - ♪ Hey! ♪
♪ One, two ♪ - ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
- ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
[upbeat music]
[欢快音乐]
- Thanks for helping us with our reality show, Dooley.
- 多利，谢谢你帮我们做真人秀。
- Yeah, you're the only guy we know who could
是的，你是我们认识的唯一一个能帮我们弄到这种摄影器材的人。
get us this kind of camera equipment.
嘿，当你需要帮助时，是谁帮你解决的？
- Hey, who helps you out when you need helping out?
我们都说是Dooley。
all: Dooley do.
当你需要四套相配的盔甲时，
- When you needed four matching suits of armor,
是谁帮你弄到的？
who got 'em for you?
我们都说是Dooley。
all: Dooley do.
还有当你需要四套潜水服、一个开锁工具，
- And when you needed four wetsuits, a lock pick,
以及200支装满希腊酸奶的水枪时，
and 200 water guns filled with Greek yogurt,
是谁帮你弄到的？
who got 'em for you?
我们都说是Dooley。
all: Dooley do!
所有人: Dooley做的!
- Uh, wouldn't it be "Dooley did"?
- 呃, 不应该是 'Dooley做了' 吗?
- Depends on when Dooley do it.
- 这取决于Dooley什么时候做的。
Now let Dooley show you what he done.
现在让Dooley展示他做了什么。
In addition to the Dooley-cam...
除了Dooley-cam之外...
I've also hidden cameras downstairs, upstairs,
我还在楼下、楼上、你父母的店里——几乎所有你会去的地方都藏了摄像头。
in your parents' store--pretty much everywhere you're gonna go.
我甚至在狗身上也装了一个。
I've even got one on the dog.
（打响指）
[snaps fingers]
- 他让我也戴一个。
- He asked me to wear one.
我拒绝了。
I said no.
我说不行。
- Now here's your portable Quadfessional.
- 现在这是你的便携式Quadfessional。
This is where you can escape and get things off your chest.
这是你可以逃避并倾诉心事的地方。
- Oh, I got things on my chest.
- 哦，我胸口确实有东西。
It totally works.
完全有效。
This chocolate chip came right off my chest.
这个巧克力碎片从我胸口直接掉下来了。
- That's a mole.
- 那是个痣。
- Either way, it popped right off.
- 不管怎样，它直接就掉了。
- Anyway...
- 总之...
I can control all the cameras right here from this tablet.
我可以从这个平板电脑上控制所有的摄像头。
- Dooley, this is incredible.
杜利，这太不可思议了。
- Yeah, but where did you get all this--
是啊，但你从哪儿弄到这些——
- Eh, eh, eh. - Wait, this stuff isn't--
呃，呃，呃。——等等，这些东西不是——
- Jee, jee, jee.
吉，吉，吉。
The less you know, the better.
知道得越少越好。
- That's always worked for me.
这对我一直很管用。
- No one else is concerned about where all the--
难道其他人都不关心这些东西从哪儿来的吗？
- Zub, bub, bub. - You can't--
祖，布，布。——你不能——
- Bap! - But I--
啪！——但我——
- Bap, bap, bap, bap.
啪，啪，啪，啪。
- All right, I'm dropping it, but I am not comfortable.
好的，我放下它，但我并不舒服。
- Now let's do this.
现在让我们开始吧。
The faster we shoot this, the faster we get rich and famous.
我们拍得越快，就能越快变得富有和出名。
- And the faster we can watch whatever we want.
而且我们也能越快想看什么就看什么。
- Okay, camera's rolling.
好的，摄像机开始拍摄了。
Just act normal.
就表现得正常一点。
And...
然后...
Action.
开始。
[static]
[静电声]
[dramatic music]
[戏剧性音乐]
- [whispering] This is totally lame.
- [低语] 这真是太逊了。
- Do something interesting. - You do something interesting!
- 做点有趣的事。 - 你做点有趣的事！
- I'll do something interesting.
- 我会做点有趣的事。
Table flip!
掀桌子！
♪ ♪
I'm pretty sure that table's nailed to the floor.
我很确定那桌子是钉在地上的。
Guys, a little help here.
伙计们，帮帮忙。
[all grunting]
[所有人哼哼唧唧]
- Come on, come on. - Okay.
- 快点，快点。 - 好吧。
[all grunting]
[所有人哼哼唧唧]
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
- So turns out, we weren't as interesting as we thought.
- 结果证明，我们并没有自己想象的那么有趣。
But it didn't take long for us to figure out
但我们很快就找到了
how to make it more "quad-dacious."
如何让它变得更加“引人入胜”。
- Guess what.
- 猜猜看。
Someone in this room has a birthday coming up.
我们房间里有人即将过生日。
- Oh, is it me?
- 哦，是我吗？
- No.
- 不是。
- Is it you?
- 是你吗？
- We have the same birthday.
我们同一天生日。
- Oh.
哦。
Is it us?
是我们吗？
- No, it's Mae.
不，是梅。
- So what do you want to do for your birthday this year?
那你今年生日想怎么过？
Big party?
大派对？
The best reality shows have really big parties.
最好的真人秀节目确实有大派对。
And big parties always have
而大派对总是有
tension, arguments, and drama.
紧张、争吵和戏剧。
All the good stuff.
所有精彩的部分。
- I don't want a party.
- 我不想办派对。
Too much drama.
太多戏剧了。
- Oh, nonsense!
- 哦，胡说！
It's your birthday.
这是你的生日。
- Yeah, but you guys always...
- 是啊，但你们总是...
how to I put this gently?
我该怎么委婉地说呢？
Completely ruin my birthday parties.
完全毁了我的生日派对。
- I wouldn't say completely.
- 我不会说完全毁了。
- Last year, Dicky blew out my candle.
- 去年，迪基吹灭了我的蜡烛。
- Who hasn't accidentally blown out someone's candle?
- 谁没不小心吹灭过别人的蜡烛呢？
- With his barf.
- 用他的呕吐物。
- That was your fault for having a hotdog-eating contest.
- 那是你自己的错，谁让你举办热狗大胃王比赛。
- It wasn't a contest. Those were for everybody.
- 那不是比赛。那些热狗是给大家的。
- Okay, so, last year, I admit, not your best birthday.
- 好吧，所以，去年，我承认，不是你最好的生日。
- And the year before?
- 还有前一年呢？
- Hey, you served sloppy Joes before you let us
- 嘿，你让我们在跳跳屋之前吃了 sloppy Joes。
in the bounce house.
- 那不是我们的错。
That was not on us.
- 不，那是其他人的错。
- No, it was on everybody else.
- 好吧，我想我们都可以承认我们吃太多然后吐了很多。
- Okay, I think we can all agree we overeat and throw up a lot.
- 如果我们保证不吃任何东西，你会让我们补偿你吗？
- If we promise not to eat anything,
如果我们保证不吃东西，
will you let us make it up to you
你会让我们弥补过错，并在今年为你举办派对吗？
and throw you a party this year?
拜托？
all: Please?
好吧！
- Fine!
但没什么大不了的，只有我们。
But nothing big, just us. - Got it.
没问题，没什么大不了的——好主意。
Nothing big--great idea.
糟糕的主意！
Terrible idea!
“没什么大不了的”？
"Nothing big"?
说得多无聊啊！
Talk about boring! - Right?
对吧？
Who wants to watch that?
谁想看那个？
- Hey, get out of my Quadfessional!
嘿，离开我的四分之一专业！
- Hey get out of Ricky's Quadfessional!
嘿，离开里基的四分之一专业！
- But I want to make sure we're not gonna have a lame party.
但我想要确保我们不会举办一个无聊的派对。
- Nicky's right.
尼基说得对。
Think about how bad that'd be for us.
想想那对我们有多糟糕。
I-I mean Mae.
我的意思是梅。
This is all about Mae.
这都是关于梅的。
- Yeah!
是的！
Mae.
梅。
♪ ♪
[upbeat music]
- So, when you say you want your party to be
just us, you mean, like,
just us and 50 people, right?
- Dawn. - All right.
What about 45? - Dawn!
- Fine, 20 guests. No more.
- We're going to need a theme. - A theme?
- How about cats? Mae likes cats.
- 猫咪怎么样？梅喜欢猫咪。
- I do like cats.
- 我确实喜欢猫咪。
- We got this, Mae.
- 我们搞得定，梅。
- Oh, she also likes root beer floats.
- 哦，她还喜欢根汁啤酒漂浮。
- I do like root beer floats!
- 我确实喜欢根汁啤酒漂浮！
- Mae, please.
- 梅，请。
- We can it a "Mae's Favorite Things" party.
- 我们可以称之为“梅的最爱”派对。
- Love it! - Awesome.
- 太棒了！ - 太好了。
- That really ties it all together.
- 这确实把一切都串联起来了。
- Okay, fine.
- 好吧，好吧。
20 friends, a few things I like, but that's it.
20个朋友，几样我喜欢的东西，就这样。
You guys have to promise me this party won't get huge.
你们得答应我这个派对不会搞得太大。
all: We promise.
我们都答应。
all: We lied.
我们撒谎了。
♪ ♪
- Oh heck to the no, massage lady.
- 哦，绝对不行，按摩女士。
I'm not just gonna stand here and take that.
- 我不会就这样站在这里接受这个。
- Yeah, you cross the toilet paper princess,
- 是的，你惹了卫生纸公主，
you get straight-up flushed.
- 你就直接被冲走了。
- Ka-floosh.
- 卡-弗鲁什。
Boom.
砰。
[door opens]
[门打开]
- What you doing, Tom?
你在做什么，汤姆？
- Just being a good dad and keeping tabs on
只是作为一个好爸爸，关注孩子们在看什么。
what the kids are watching.
我必须告诉你...
And I have got to tell you...
这真是天才！
it's genius!
不，不，亲爱的。
- No, no, honey.
真人秀太假了，而且虚伪，还有--
Reality TV is so phony, and fake, and--
她为什么对那个按摩师那么刻薄？
why is she being so mean to that masseuse?
因为她嘲笑她的“雪擦”卫生纸广告。
- Because she made fun of her "Snow Wipe"
因为她取笑了她的“雪擦”
toilet paper commercial.
卫生纸广告。
- What?
什么？
I don't wipe my tushy without thinking of her face.
我每次擦屁股都会想到她的脸。
- Right?
对吧？
I'm gonna say what I said to you on our wedding night.
我要再说一遍我们婚礼晚上对你说的话。
Let's go on this journey together, Anne.
让我们一起踏上这段旅程，安妮。
- [laughs]
[笑]
- Now take your massage table,
现在带着你的按摩桌，
and get out!
出去！
[both screaming]
[两人尖叫]
- I can't believe she just flipped a massage table!
- 我真不敢相信她刚刚掀翻了一张按摩床！
- She flips a table in every episode.
- 她每集都会掀翻一张桌子。
- I am so happy to be on this journey with you--
- 我很高兴能和你一起踏上这段旅程——
- Then help me!
- 那就帮我！
[both grunting]
[两人哼哼]
And don't worry, there's no way the kids could possibly know
别担心，孩子们绝对不可能知道
what we're watching right now.
我们现在在看什么。
[both grunting]
[两人哼哼]
- Ugh, what is in this thing?
- 呃，这里面是什么？
♪ ♪
- Root beer float fixings.
- 根啤漂浮配料。
Check.
检查。
30 kitties for the cat petting zoo.
30只猫咪用于猫咪抚摸动物园。
Check.
检查。
- Wait, where did we get 30 cats?
- 等等，我们从哪里弄来30只猫的？
- Yut-dut-dut!
- 尤特-杜特-杜特！
Better you don't know.
你最好不知道。
- Cake candles. Check.
- 蛋糕蜡烛。检查。
Party music. Check.
派对音乐。检查。
- Lame check list--
- 无聊的检查清单——
all: Check!
大家: 检查！
- This list is not lame!
- 这个清单才不无聊！
- This list is sucking all the fun out of this world.
- 这个清单正在吸走这个世界的所有乐趣。
- Trust me, we need this list.
- 相信我，我们需要这个清单。
It's gonna help us make sure Mae's party is problem-free.
它将帮助我们确保梅的派对没有问题。
- Problem-free?
- 没有问题？
But without problems, there'll be no drama.
但没有问题，就没有戏剧性。
- Without drama, there'll be no show.
- 没有戏剧性，就没有表演。
- Without a show, we're never gonna be able to
- 没有表演，我们就永远无法
jet ski in a lake filled with ice cream.
在满是冰淇淋的湖上玩水上摩托。
- I thought it was a pool full of pudding?
- 我以为是个满是布丁的泳池？
- I'm thinking big, people!
- 我在想大的，各位！
We needed drama.
我们需要戏剧性。
And if we've learned anything from "The Life of Eiffel"
而如果我们从《艾菲尔的生活》中学到了什么
it's that nothing stirs up a little "party drama"
那就是没有什么比告诉某人他们不能再来了更能迅速激起“派对戏剧”的。
quicker than telling someone they can't come anymore.
所以让我们开始搅动吧。
So let's start stirring.
- 我的好搅拌勺。
- My good stirring spoon.
♪ ♪
- Bad news, Mae.
- 坏消息，Mae。
Ricky just went over the guest list,
Ricky刚刚审核了宾客名单，
and he says it's ballooned up to 21.
他说人数已经膨胀到21人了。
And since you really, really wanted to keep it to 20 guests,
既然你真的，真的很想把人数控制在20人，
I guess there's only one thing we can do.
我想我们只能做一件事了。
You're gonna have to cut somebody.
你得砍掉一个人。
- No, that's okay.
- 不用了，没关系。
I could live with 21. - Did I say 21?
我可以接受21人。 - 我说21人了吗？
I meant 22.
我的意思是22人。
So, who's getting the boot?
那么，谁会被踢出去呢？
What about Miles?
那Miles呢？
- Nah, that's okay.
- 不了，没关系。
- 22 is fine. - No, no, no.
- 22个可以。 - 不，不，不。
You said 20 was your limit and we need to
你说过20是你的极限，我们需要
respect your wishes.
尊重你的意愿。
- Yeah, but I just don't want anyone to feel left out.
- 是的，但我只是不想让任何人感到被排除。
That's too much drama.
那太戏剧化了。
- Yeah, drama.
- 是的，戏剧化。
Who wants that? [laughs]
谁想要那个？[笑]
And girlfriend doesn't like drama.
而且女朋友不喜欢戏剧。
- Well, if girlfriend won't un-invite someone
- 好吧，如果女朋友不愿意从她的派对中取消邀请某人，
from her party,
也许我们应该像真正的真人秀那样，
maybe we should just do what real reality shows do
投票决定我们中的一个人出局。
and vote one of ourselves out.
- 有意思。
- Interesting.
- 那可能行得通。 - 非常戏剧化。
- That could work. - Very dramatic.
- 好吧，就这么定了。
- All right, it's settled.
我们将投票，到今晚结束时，
We'll vote, and by the end of the night,
我们中的一个人将不会去Mae的派对。
one of us won't be going to Mae's party.
- 但会是谁呢？
- But who?
- Little does Nicky know, I'm already plotting his demise.
- 尼基不知道，我已经在策划他的失败了。
I know exactly who is going to get voted out.
我确切知道谁会被投票出局。
Me?
我吗？
I got voted out?
我被投票出局了？
- Apparently, he didn't know exactly
- 显然，他并不确切知道
who was going to get voted out.
谁会被投票出局。
- Ricky is not happy!
- 瑞奇很不高兴！
- Drama. Check.
- 戏剧性。确认。
[upbeat music]
[欢快音乐]
♪ ♪
- I can't believe you voted me out!
- 我真不敢相信你把我投出去了！
- Isn't this what you wanted?
- 这不是你想要的吗？
- Yeah, wasn't it your idea to have the vote
- 是啊，不是你提议要投票的吗？
in the first place?
- 那是因为我当时以为我有足够的票数！
- That was when I thought I had the numbers!
- 我们有过联盟的！
We had an alliance!
- 你答应过我会投票给Nicky的。
You promised me you'd vote for Nicky.
- 我有吗？
- I did?
[狗在低吼]
[dog growling]
- 听着，如果我能说服Dawn投票给Nicky，
- Listen, if I get Dawn to vote for Nicky,
- 你会投票给他吗？
will you vote for him, too?
你会投票给他吗？
- Yes!
是的！
- You said yes!
你说过是的！
- Only because that was the first time
只是因为那是我第一次
I ever beat Squishy in a tug-o-war.
在拔河比赛中赢过Squishy。
I mean...
我的意思是...
I could have beat him before, but he cheats.
我本可以在之前赢他，但他作弊。
- [whimpers]
（呜咽声）
- You promised to vote for Nicky, too.
你也承诺过投票给Nicky。
- I know.
我知道。
But that was before he made us...
但那是在他让我们...
this.
变成这样之前。
- Sometimes you have to fight fire with flan.
- 有时候你得用布丁来对抗火焰。
- You know what? It's fine.
- 你知道吗？没关系。
If you don't want me at the party, I won't go!
如果你不想我在派对上，我就不去！
In fact, maybe I should just drop out of this whole thing.
事实上，也许我应该退出这一切。
- What whole thing?
- 什么一切？
- This stupid show.
- 这个愚蠢的节目。
I'm not "Hanging with the Harpers" anymore.
我不再是“与哈珀一家hang out”了。
I quit!
我退出！
[grunts]
[咕哝声]
[roars]
[咆哮声]
- I got to admit, I'm gonna miss his persistence.
- 我得承认，我会想念他的坚持。
- You know what you're also gonna miss?
- 你知道你还会想念什么吗？
My checklist!
我的清单！
No Ricky, no list-y. - No biggie.
没有Ricky，就没有清单。- 没什么大不了的。
- Yes, biggie! - Oh, please-y.
- 是的，大不了！- 哦，拜托。
I think we can pull off Mae's party without your list.
我认为我们可以在没有你的清单的情况下办好Mae的派对。
- Good luck.
- 祝你好运。
Without this list, you'll have no idea
没有这个清单，你将毫无头绪
how to make the party a success.
没有这份清单，你将不知道如何让派对成功。
Ricky out!
Ricky退出！
[grumbling]
[咕哝声]
- You know what?
- 你知道吗？
This list just gave me a great idea for this party.
这份清单给了我一个关于派对的好主意。
Confetti!
五彩纸屑！
♪ ♪
- Next season on "The Life of Eiffel"...
- 下一季在《埃菲尔的生活》...
- With me, Eiffel!
- 和我一起，埃菲尔！
- The tables are turned...
- 局势逆转了...
- [gasps]
[倒抽一口气]
Whoever flipped my table is gonna pay.
不管谁翻了我的桌子，都得付出代价。
- Yeah, someone's getting flushed.
没错，有人要遭殃了。
- Not now.
现在不行。
I'm not in the mood to ka-floosh.
我没心情来个‘哗啦’。
- You know, we have to be at the store early
你知道的，我们得早点去店里
to set up for Mae's party.
为梅的派对做准备。
We should probably stop watching and get to bed.
我们可能应该停止观看，去睡觉了。
- Tom!
汤姆！
I thought we were on this journey together!
我以为我们是一起踏上这段旅程的！
I'm not going to bed until I find out who turned that table.
我非得找出是谁转了那张桌子才去睡觉。
- I have never loved you more.
- 我从未如此爱你。
[door opens]
[门打开]
- Hide! - Oh, oh!
- 藏起来！ - 哦，哦！
No, no, honey, close it. - Slide it, slide it--
不，不，亲爱的，关上它。 - 推过去，推过去——
- Close it, just close it-- - Slide it, slide it--
- 关上它，就关上它—— - 推过去，推过去——
[muffled] - One of your friends, Eiffel.
[模糊] - 是你的一个朋友，埃菲尔。
- What? La, la, la, la.
- 什么？啦，啦，啦，啦。
La, la, la, la, la la.
啦，啦，啦，啦，啦啦。
Oops.
哎呀。
It just slipped right out of my hand.
它就这么从我手里滑出去了。
- Just having some ice cream. - Mmm.
- 只是吃点冰淇淋。 - 嗯。
- What're you doing?
- 你在干什么？
- So my parents have lost their minds.
- 我父母完全疯了。
But in other news, the party is coming together great.
但好消息是，派对准备得很好。
Mae is gonna love it.
Mae一定会喜欢的。
♪ ♪
- I don't love it.
- 我不喜欢。
It's all just too much.
这一切都太过分了。
- Great party, Mae.
- 派对很棒，Mae。
- I know!
- 我知道！
Isn't it all just too much?
是不是一切都太过分了？
I still don't love it.
我还是不喜欢。
- Don't worry!
- 别担心！
You will.
你会喜欢的。
We have a lot more planned.
我们还有很多计划。
- There's more?
- 还有更多？
Ugh.
呃。
- Despite Mae's hesitance, the party was shaping up
- 尽管Mae有些犹豫，但派对正在成为我们需要的
to be exactly what we needed to make our show a success
让我们的演出成功
and make us rich and famous.
并且让我们变得富有和出名。
- Hey!
嘿！
Ladies.
女士们。
- Um, what're you doing here? - We voted you out.
嗯，你们在这里做什么？ - 我们投票让你出局了。
- Your vote is irrelevant,
你的投票无关紧要，
since I am no longer on your silly reality show.
因为我不再参加你们那愚蠢的真人秀了。
- That "silly reality show" is your reality.
那“愚蠢的真人秀”是你的现实。
- Not anymore.
不再是了。
As you can see, I now have my own show.
如你所见，我现在有自己的节目。
It's called "Strictly Ricky."
它叫做“Strictly Ricky”。
Now if you'll excuse me.
现在，如果不介意的话。
- Okay, there is no way "Strictly Ricky"
- 好了，‘Ricky严选’绝不可能
is stealing our party.
抢走我们的派对风头。
Now, Dicky, grab a cat and meet me at the throne.
Dicky，抱只猫过来，王座那里见我。
Queen Mae needs a lap kitty.
女王Mae需要一只膝上猫。
- Nice crown!
- 漂亮的王冠！
[whispers] Don't look at the camera.
（低声说）别看镜头。
- How can I not?
- 我怎么能不看？
It's right in my face.
就在我的面前。
- [laughs]
- （笑）
Oh, Mae, you're too funny.
哦，梅，你太有趣了。
Too bad you're stuck hanging with the Harpers.
可惜你只能和哈珀一家混在一起。
You'd be a star on my show.
你在我节目里一定会成为明星的。
- But I thought it was called "Strictly Ricky"?
- 但我以为节目叫《严格里奇》？
- Well, I'm thinking of changing it to
- 嗯，我在考虑改成
"Strictly Ricky! And Sometimes Mae."
《严格里奇！有时还有梅》。
- [giggles nervously]
- [紧张地咯咯笑]
There's my best friend and the birthday girl.
那是我的好朋友和寿星。
Come on, it's kitten time.
来吧，现在是小猫时间。
- She was talking to me.
- 她在跟我说话。
On my camera.
在我的相机上。
On my show.
在我的节目上。
- She was on our show first.
她先上我们的节目。
- Let go! - Come on, man.
放手！快点，伙计。
- You like us better, right? - Let go!
你更喜欢我们，对吧？放手！
- Guys, stop it, you're hurting me!
伙计们，别这样，你们弄疼我了！
- Stop making this all about you, Mae.
别总是把一切都扯到你自己身上，Mae。
- But it's my birthday!
但今天是我的生日！
- You're right.
你说得对。
It is your birthday.
今天是你的生日。
So it's time we sang to you.
所以是时候为你唱生日歌了。
Everybody gather round.
大家围过来。
Time to sing "Happy Birthday."
该唱《生日快乐》了。
Wait till you see the little surprise
等着看那个小惊喜吧
that wasn't on your list.
那可是你清单上没有的。
As soon as the song ends, Dooley's gonna fire off
歌曲一结束，杜利就会启动
all those confetti canons.
所有的彩带炮。
- Don't know how, why, or when,
不知道为什么，也不知道何时，
but somehow, you'll screw it up.
但不知怎么的，你总会搞砸。
- Not gonna happen.
不会发生的。
Oh, excuse me.
哦，对不起。
Dicky, what're you doing?
迪基，你在干什么？
Mae should have--
梅应该有--
where are all the cats?
所有的猫都去哪儿了？
- They're playing in their cat tubes.
- 它们在猫隧道里玩呢。
- What cat tubes? - All of 'em!
- 什么猫隧道？- 所有的！
[dramatic music]
- Those are for confetti!
- 那些是用来放彩纸的！
Dooley, don't set off those can--
杜利，别触发那些彩--
No cats were harmed in what you're about to see.
你即将看到的画面中，没有猫受到伤害。
But do not try this at home.
但请不要在家尝试这个。
Ever.
永远不要。
For any reason.
任何理由都不行。
[record scratching] Canons!
大炮！
[cats meowing]
猫咪在喵喵叫。
- This is a cat-tastrophe!
这是一场猫咪灾难！
[cat meowing]
猫咪在喵喵叫。
- This is all your fault!
这都是你的错！
- Cat butt on my face!
猫屁股在我脸上！
Cat butt on my face!
Get it off!
拿开！
- My fault? How is this my fault?
我的错？这怎么是我的错？
- 'Cause if it wasn't for you, we wouldn't even be here!
因为如果不是因为你，我们根本不会在这里！
- Enough!
够了！
This is the worst birthday party ever.
这是有史以来最糟糕的生日派对。
- What do you mean?
你什么意思？
At least nobody threw up on your cake.
至少没有人把蛋糕弄脏。
[cat meowing, vomiting]
（猫叫，呕吐声）
- Ugh!
呃！
The cat yakked on the cake.
猫把蛋糕弄脏了。
- And I stand corrected.
- 我承认我错了。
- I can't believe you guys!
- 真不敢相信你们！
both: It's his fault! - It's their fault!
都是他的错！ - 都是他们的错！
- You're all at fault!
- 你们都有责任！
I didn't want any of this.
我根本不想要这些。
But you were so wrapped up in creating drama for your show,
但你们为了自己的节目制造戏剧性，
that you ruined another one of my birthdays.
又一次毁了我的生日。
Oh, and I finally decided who I want to un-invite for my party.
哦，我终于决定要取消谁的邀请了。
Me!
我！
Who's the queen of the reality show now?
现在谁是真人秀的女王？
See, when I realized they were messing up my birthday again,
你看，当我意识到他们又要搞砸我的生日时，
I decided to get something out of it.
我决定从中捞点好处。
My own spinoff.
我要搞个自己的衍生剧。
I'm gonna call it, "No One Does Drama Like Mama."
我要给它取名，“没人比妈妈更会搞事。”
Boom.
砰。
- Mae?
梅？
We're sorry.
我们很抱歉。
- All of us.
我们所有人。
- We were selfish jerks.
我们太自私了。
- We were so focused on our fake reality,
我们太沉迷于我们的虚假现实，
we screwed up our real one.
我们搞砸了我们的真实生活。
- And it wasn't worth it.
- 而且这不值得。
- Yeah, being rich and famous became more important than our friendship.
- 是的，富有和出名变得比我们的友谊更重要。
You would never do that to us.
你绝不会那样对我们。
- Yeah, you'd never get caught up in this kind of drama.
- 是的，你绝不会陷入这种戏剧性的事件。
- Yeah. Drama.
- 是的。戏剧。
Who wants that?
谁想要那个？
♪ ♪
- We didn't think you'd see. - And I didn't really mean--
- 我们没想到你会看到。 - 我并不是真的想——
- Maybe we should give up reality TV for a while.
- 也许我们应该暂时放弃真人秀。
- And delete this and never show it to anyone.
- 并且删除这个，永远不要给任何人看。
Ever.
永远。
all: Deal.
所有人: 成交。
[dog barks]
[狗叫]
- All right.
- 好吧。
♪ ♪
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
- [whistling]
- [吹口哨]
♪ ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
♪ 是的，是的，是的，是的 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 是的！ ♪
- ♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 是的，是的，是的，是的 ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 是的！ ♪